https://baseballdirect.com/order-information/privacy-policy/

HOMEWORLD SERIESWorld Series Videos by YearWS 1940sWS 1950sWS 1960sWS 1970sWS 1980sWS 1990sWS 2000sWS 2010sWorld Series by TeamBASEBALL VIDEOSWorld SeriesBiographiesTeam History VideosTeams InformationRare Baseball FilmMiscellaneousMoviesCollege BaseballBASEBALL AUDIOComplete Game BroadcastsAudio 1920sAudio 1930sAudio 1940sAudio 1950sAudio 1960sAudio 1960Audio 1961Audio 1962Audio 1963Audio 1964Audio 1965Audio 1966Audio 1967Audio 1968Audio 1969Audio 1970sAudio 1970Audio 1971Audio 1972Audio 1973Audio 1974Audio 1975Audio 1976Audio 1977Audio 1978Audio 1979Audio 1980sAudio 1990sClassic Audio ProgramsHighlight RecordingsBroadcastersBROADCASTERSBOOKSGIFTSTeam Alarm ClocksTeam Wall ClocksTeam Floor MatsTeam License Plate FramesTeam CoastersStadium BaseballsPanoramic Stadium PrintsNecktiesCalendarsBobbleheadsCONTACT USAsk a QuestionTEAMSYou are here: Home / Order Information / Privacy PolicyBaseball Direct’s Privacy Policy StatementThis is the web site of Baseball Direct, Inc.
Our postal address is
P.O. Box 7563
Charlottesville, VA 22906
We can be reached via e-mail at info@baseballdirect.com
or you can reach us by telephone at (800) 558-6273Your privacy and the security of your information is very important to us. We take precautions to protect your privacy and data. For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server and security software automatically recognizes and records the consumer’s domain name, and IP Address, but not the e-mail address or any other personal information. This information is held for a limited amount of time.We do collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. When a customer purchases a product they may set up an account in our system, and we will collect name, address, phone number and email address and credit card information for the purposes of fulfilling the order. We do not sell any customer information to third parties. Credit card information is separated in the transmission process for security purposes, and the card number is not stored on our servers.The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website, to process your order, and used to notify consumers about updates to our website. We do not sell customer information with any third parties for marketing purposes. We do use the customer’s email address to send them periodic updates of new products and promotional offers. Customers receiving these emails always have the ability to opt out of these communications. We assume if you purchase products from us that you are interested in knowing about new product offerings and special sales promotions. We never sell customer information to third parties.With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart. Account information is maintained for the convenience of customers to easily log in for repeat purchasing of products.If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at info@baseballdirect.com, calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address. We do not sell our customers’ email addresses.Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online. We do not sell the phone numbers of our customers.From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.With respect to security: We use industry-standard encryption technologies through SSL (Secure Socket Layer) when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. We take steps to ensure the information provided through our website is kept secure.If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, The DMA’s Committee on Ethical Business Practices at pfaley@the-dma.orgThe Best of Baseball Comes from Baseball Direct!Search for Products
Product Categories- Select Category -BroadcastersBaseball Videos-Team History Videos-Rare Film Videos-Biography Videos-Movies-Miscellaneous Baseball Videos-World Series Videos--World Series Videos, Year---WS 1940s---WS 1950s---WS 1960s---WS 1970s---WS 1980s---WS 1990s---WS 2000s---WS 2010s---WS 2020s--World Series Videos, Team-College BaseballBaseball Audio-Audio Broadcasts--Audio 1930s--Audio 1940s--Audio 1920s--Audio 1950s--Audio 1960s---Audio 1961---Audio 1962---Audio 1963---Audio 1964---Audio 1965---Audio 1966---Audio 1967---Audio 1968---Audio 1969---Audio 1960--Audio 1970s---Audio 1970---Audio 1971---Audio 1972---Audio 1973---Audio 1974---Audio 1975---Audio 1976---Audio 1977---Audio 1978---Audio 1979--Audio 1980s--Audio 1990s-Audio Programs-Audio HighlightsBaseball BooksBaseball Gifts-Alarm Clocks-Wall Clocks-Stadium Prints-License Plate Frame-Coasters-Bobbleheads-Floor Mats-Neckties-Calendars-Stadium BaseballsFootball-NFL Video-NFL Audio-College Football Video-College Football Audio
YOUR SCOREBOARD:What’s in your cart..Loading...Total: $
Our Latest Products…
Yankee Stadium Coasters
Fenway Park Coasters
1992 The Comeback: Buffalo Bills vs. Houston Oilers
1984 Dolphins-Cowboys
1990
7/ 1
Chicago (AL) 4, New York (AL) 0.
1987
7/ 7
Philadelphia 10, Cincinnati 8.
1980 10/21
Philadelphia 4, Kansas City 1.
1980 10/ 8
Houston 7, Philadelphia 4.
1980
4/10 Houston 3, Los Angeles 2.
New York Mets 2021 Wall Calendar
LOOKING FOR SOMETHING?
You can search for items by team, by player, by year, or even description snippet.NEW ITEMS FROM BASEBALL DIRECT…
Yankee Stadium Coasters
Fenway Park Coasters
Contact UsORDER BY PHONE:
1-888-244-8837
QUESTIONS?
Call: 1-800-558-6273
Mon-Fri 8am-5pm EST
Email: info@baseballdirect.comConnect with usPayment InformationOrder online securely.Shopping InformationNEWEST ITEMSORDERINGSHIPPINGFAQSASK A QUESTIONPRINTABLE ORDER FORMPRIVACY POLICYSign up for our newsletter…to know about the latest items added and sale items.
We will not share your email address.
